<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LinkupHome</string>

    <string name="welcome_language">Language</string>
    <string name="welcome_beauty">Enjoy</string>
    <string name="welcome_occurrence">From this moment</string>
    <string name="welcome_language_select">Select Language</string>

    <string name="product_manual">Product Manual</string>
    <string name="center_title">Information Centre</string>


    <string name="mesh_tab_control">Control</string>
    <string name="mesh_tab_device_select">Select Group</string>
    <string name="mesh_tab_group_setting">Create Groups</string>
    <string name="mesh_tab_device_connect">Device Connect</string>


    <string name="menu_rename">Rename</string>
    <string name="menu_timer">Timer</string>
    <string name="menu_control_share">Share Control</string>
    <string name="menu_scan">Scan</string>


    <string name="scan_get_data">Waiting for scan QR Code...</string>
    <string name="scan_qrCode">My QR Code</string>
    <string name="scan_auto">Auto-scan by putting the QR Code in frame</string>


    <string name="scene_mode">Scene Mode</string>
    <string name="scene_read">Read Mode</string>
    <string name="scene_sunset">Sunset Mode</string>
    <string name="scene_rest">Rest Mode</string>
    <string name="scene_spring">Spring Blossoms Mode</string>
    <string name="scene_rainforest">Selva Mode</string>
    <string name="scene_lighting">Lighting Mode</string>
    <string name="scene_flow">Flowing</string>


    <string name="speed_slow">Slow Speed</string>
    <string name="speed_normal">Normal Speed</string>
    <string name="speed_fast">Fast Speed</string>


    <string name="timer_open_time">Light Turn On Time</string>
    <string name="timer_close_time">Light Turn Off Time</string>
    <string name="timer_loop">Repeat</string>


    <string name="share_tips">Share the control with your family or friends</string>
    <string name="share_tip_download_app">Download the APP</string>
    <string name="share_tip_open_app">Open the APP and scan QR Code</string>
    <string name="share_tip_success">Successfully Shared</string>
    <string name="share_qrCode">QR Code</string>
    <string name="share_qrCode_generating">Generating control-sharing QR Code...</string>
    <string name="share_qrCode_generate_success">Control-sharing QR Code is generated, pls scan</string>
    <string name="share_qrCode_generate_fail">Generate QR Code failed</string>
    <string name="share_qrCode_regenerate">Regenerate QR Code</string>
    <string name="share_img_save">Save the Picture</string>
    <string name="share_img_save_success">Picture Saved</string>
    <string name="share_img_save_fail">Saving Error</string>


    <string name="group_setting_drag">Push "Add" Button to Add</string>
    <string name="group_setting_exceed_number">The number of packets exceeded</string>


    <string name="device_search">Search Device</string>
    <string name="device_associating">Connecting...</string>
    <string name="device_clear">Reset all groups?</string>
    <string name="device_associate_fail">The connection fails. Please restart the device to connect.</string>



    <string name="device_connect_step2_title">Tips</string>
    <string name="device_connect_step2_hint">If the device is not found within 10 seconds, please try to reset the device</string>


    <string name="device_reset_hint2">Please use the switch to operate:\n1. Switch off the light\n2. Switch on the light, then switch off the light after 1-2 seconds.\n3. Switch on the light again, then switch off the light after 1-2 seconds.\n4. Switch light on the third time, when the light flash 3 times, it means the device is reset to defaults.\n\n（If no light flash 3 times, please repeat above steps until reset successfully.Turning on and off the light can\'t be too fast, it takes 1-2 seconds. )</string>
    <string name="device_reset_hint1">This step suitable for there is no new device appear in the "Device connect" page after reset. If the new device auto pops up, please ignore this step.\n\nIf no new device appear in the "Device connect" page, pls left slide to delete the invalid connection, the reset light can be displayed, then click to connection.</string>

    <string name="device_reset_tip">Please try following two shortcuts firstly:</string>
    <string name="device_reset_hint0">Way 1: Turn off bluetooth, then turn on it again. \nWay 2: Exit the app completely from the background system, then restart the app.</string>
    <string name="device_reset_hint3">If you\'re still unable to find devices after trying two shortcuts, follow the steps below to reset your device.</string>


    <string name="import_error">QR code does not match</string>
    <string name="network_error">Network connection failed,please check the network settings.</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="group">Group</string>
    <string name="initialize">Reset Groups</string>

    <string name="removing">Removing...</string>
    <string name="add_product">Add Product</string>
    <string name="added">Added</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="adding">Adding...</string>

    <string name="lamp_bed">智能床头灯</string>
    <string name="lamp_rgb">RGB Bulb</string>
    <string name="lamp_outdoor">Outdoor Lamp</string>

    <string name="lamp_mini_outdoor">Mini Outdoor Lamp</string>
    <string name="lamp_cct">CCT Bulb</string>
    <string name="lamp_led_strip">Strip Light</string>


    <string name="privacy_tip">Please confirm that you have read and agree to</string>
    <string name="license_agreement">The End user License Agreement</string>
    <string name="privacy_statement">The Privacy Statement</string>
    <string name="privacy_start">start</string>

    <string name="privacy_statement_content">Effective Date: August, 1, 2018\n\nThis Privacy Statement describes how we use and disclose the information that we collect from you when you visit our website, products, applications, or services that references this Privacy Statement (collectively, the Services). Our Services are very diverse, so sometimes additional policies may apply. These additional policies Will be available with the relevant services and those additional policies become part of your agreement with us if you use those Services.\n\nFor the purposes of applicable EU data protection laws and unless otherwise stated LinkupHome is the data controller and is responsible for the collection and use of your Personal data.\n\nThis Privacy statement is incorporated into our terms of Use at http://www.ihomey.cc, please read both documents carefully, as they contain important information about your use of the services. If you do not understand our Privacy Statement or our Terms of Use, please contact us using the information below.\n\nKEY DEFINITIONS\n\n“Aggregate Information” is information that has been combined with information about other users and analyzed or evaluated as a whole, such that no specific individual may be reasonably identified. For example,Aggregate Information may include a statement that says 50%of our users have used the mobile app in the last month.\n\n“Cookies” are text files typically small in size, that are placed on your computer by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you,and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.\n\n“Personal Data" is any information that can be used to identify you, either alone or in combination with other information. Personal Data does not include aggregate information or other anonymous information (including metadata) collected by LinkupHome that cannot be used to identify you, even if such information was derived from your personal data.\n\n“Usage Data" is information about how you use the Services, such as your browser type, domains, page views duration and information about the device you use to access the services.\n\n“Web beacons" (also known as "Clear GIFs"and "Pixel Tags") are small bits of code embedded in web pages or in emails that are used to monitor the behavior of a Website user or recipient of an email.\n\nCOLLECTING AND USING YOUR PERSONAL DATA\n\nWe collect Personal data when we deliver our products, conduct marketing activities, gather feedback, provide customer supports, fulfill product orders, and run our business operations. the personal data we collect varies based upon whether you are using our Sites, Products, or other services.For the information that you provide to us during sign up or when you set up your account or profile, the information we collect may include your name, email address, telephone number, gender, date of birth,country where you reside, and other information that may help is better provide the services to you.\n\nWe may also collect information from your use of our Service, such as how you use a particular service. This information includes:\n\n•Device-specific information. We collect device specific information(such as your hardware model operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information).\n\n•Log information. When you use our Services, we automatically collect and store certain information in server logs, such as Usage Data, usage detail and device event information(e.g, crashes, system activity,hardware settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request, and referral URL.\n\n•Location information. We may collect and process information about your actual location We use various technologies to determine location including IP address, GPS, and other sensors. For example, if our Service can provide driving direction, traffic reporting recommendation of establishments near your location and similar services, then we may collect your device\'s real-time or compiled geographical information in order to provide such Service to you.\n\n•Unique application numbers. Certain Services include a unique application number. this number and information about your installation(for example, the operating system type and application version number) may be sent to us at the time of installation or update.\n\n•Information we collect when you are signed in to our Services may be associated with your account. When Information is associated with your account we treat it as personal information.\n\nIn addition to the purposes listed above, we may also use your personal data to:\n\n•Communicate with you Obtain your name for purposes of communicating with you and identifying you as a user of the website or product.\n\n•Verify your identity. We may use your Personal Data to verify who you are. For example, we may verify your age or that you have obtained your parent\'s or guardian\'s permission to use the website or product.\n\n•Send you marketing materials. We may send you marketing materials, such as promotional emails or catalogue, to keep you informed of our upcoming product releases. You generally must opt-in to receiving. Our marketing materials, and you may opt out of receiving them at any time. For more information on how to opt out, please see YOUR CHOICES below.\n\n•Respond to your questions and fulfill your requests.We may send you communications upon your request or otherwise with your consent.\n\n•Provide support and receive feedback. We may request Personal data in order to provide support to you. We may also collect Personal Data that are associated with your feedback .\n\n•Process your transactions. We may use your Personal Data that you provide to us in the process of making a purchase to confirm your use of a valid credit card (or other authorized methods of payment),process your payment via a credit card (or other authorized methods of payment), and send you the products.\n\nWe also gather non-descriptive, non-identifiable statistical information about how many visitors use our Services. how our users use the services how our users access certain content available on our services. How long our users access certain content, what content our users are accessing, and our user preferences or settings for certain Services. We use this aggregated Information for statistical analysis of how users make use of the services so we can better improve our Services.\n\nDATA COLLECTION TECHNOLOGIES\n\nWe use Cookies. Web Beacons and other data collection technologies (together, "Data Collection Technologies") to provide you with a better experience When you use the services. Data Collection Technologies help you log onto the Services, remember your settings and preferences, help us keep your information safe and secure, and enable our partners to serve ads for our products and services, including those targeted to your interests. While the data Collection Technologies we use may change from time to time, they generally fall into the following categories.\n\n•Authentication, We use cookies to verify your account and determine when you are logged in so we can make it easier for you to access the services and show you the appropriate experience and features.\n\n•Security and product integrity, we use cookies to help us keep your account and information safe and secure. We also use cookies to combat activity that violates our policies or otherwise degrades our ability to provide our services.\n\n•Advertising, insights and measurement. We use cookies to help us show ads for businesses and other organizations to people who may be interested in the products, services or causes they promote. We also use cookies to help measure the performance of ad campaigns for businesses that use the Services Cookies help us serve and measure ads across different browsers and devices used by the same person.\n\n•Site features and services, we use cookies to enable the functionality that helps us provide the services and provide you with the best experience possible, including to help provide you with content relevant to your locale.\n\n•Analytics and research: We use Cookies to better understand how people use the website so that we can improve the Services. For example, we partner with Google analytics, which uses Cookies to track your interactions with our Services. Google then collects that information and reports it to us, without identifying individual users. This information helps us improve our Services so that we can better serve users like you. For more information on Google analytic visit https:// support. google. com/analytics\n\nAlthough most browsers and devices accept Cookies and other data Collection Technologies by default, their settings usually allow you to clear or decline Cookies. If you disable Cookies, some of the features of our Services may not be available or function properly.\n\nInterest Based Advertising: We may use vendors to serve advertisements on our behalf across the internet These advertising vendors may collect(through the use of data Collection technologies) non-identifiable information about your visits to and interactions with our Services. In addition our vendors may also use the information about your visits to other websites to target advertisements for products and services available from us. If you would like more information about this practice, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative(NAI)at http://optout.networkadvertising.org.\n\nPlease note: Some web browsers incorporate a "Do not Track" feature (DNT) that signals to the websites that you visit that you do not want to have your online activity tracked. Many websites and applications,including our Services, do not currently respond to web browser DNT signals because such signals are not yet uniform. For more information about DNT signals, please visit http://allaboutdnt.com\n\nSHARING YOUR PERSONAL DATA\n\nBecause we know your personal data is important to you, we may share your information for the reason(s) disclosed to you at the time we collect it, with your consent, as well as in the following ways:\n\n•At your direction. We will share your information with third parties if and when you direct us to. For example, you may ask us to share your Personal Data when you wish to interact with other users or post certain information on social media\n\n•With our Vendors. We may share your Personal Data with our Vendors as necessary to enable them to provide services to us. Vendors are third parties(other companies and individuals)that support the operation and maintenance of our services\n\n•With our Partners. We may allow certain third parties, such as car manufacturers or electronic consumer device manufacturers, to integrate components of our services into their own devices and software. These third parties will use our platform to access your information to facilitate our services on their device or software. They may elect to collect or use your information using our platform without our knowledge. These third parties are separately responsible for their own privacy policies and practices In addition we may collect information about these third party devices or software that you use to help us provide core functions of our Services\n\n•With our commonly owned entities. We may share your Personal Data with other companies under common ownership and control of LinkupHome, which may include our subsidiaries, corporate parent, or any other subsidiaries owned by our corporate parent. We do this in order to provide you better service and improve your experience.\n\n•For legal purposes.\nWe may share your Personal Data as reasonably necessary to comply with law or a legal process (including a court or government order or subpoena), to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues to enforce this Privacy statement and/or the terms of use and to protect the rights property or safety of LinkupHome, our users, and/or the public.\n\n•During a corporate transaction. If LinkupHome is involved in a merger, acquisition, financing or sale business or assets information collected from and about users may be transferred to one or more third parties involved in such transaction and, upon such transfer, the relevant third party privacy policy or policies may govern further use of the information.\n\nYOUR CHOICES\n\nYour preferences about how we use your information are important to us and, when possible, we aim to honor them We offer the following choices that you can exercise with regard to your Personal data.\n\n•Access, modify, or delete your Personal Data. You can contact us at any time to request to access, modify or delete the personal data we possess about you.Please refer to the Contact us"section below.\n\n•Opt out of marketing communications. You can opt out of marketing communications by indicating you preference when you sign up for our Services. You may also contact us to opt out of our marketing communications.\n\n•Managing cookies and other data Collection Technologies. You have a number of options to control or limit how we and our vendors use cookies and other Data Collection Technologies including for advertising:\n\n-To prevent location information from being collected by us at any time, you can turn off your device\'s location-tracking functionality\n\n-To prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, you can install Google\'s opt-out browser add on [https://tools.googlecom/dlpage/gaoptout]\n\n-To opt out of interest-based advertising, you can visit http://optout.networkadvertising.org and follow NAIs on-screen instructions. Note that if you opt out through the NAL, you will still receive advertising, but the advertising will not be tailored to your interests. In addition, if you opt out through NAl and later delete your Cookies, use a different browser, or buy a new device, you will need you opt out of interest-based advertising again\n\n-To opt out of ads on Facebook or Google that are targeted to your interests use your Facebook [https://www.facebook.com/ads/settings] or Google Ads [https: //adssettings. google.com ] settings\n\nCheck your mobile device for settings that control ads based on your interactions with the applications on your device. For example, on your iOS device, enable the"Limit Ad Tracking"setting, and on your Android device, enable the"opt out of Ads personalization setting.\n\nPROTECTING YOUR PERSONAL DATA \n\nWe use reasonable organizational and technical security measures designed to preserve the security of your Personal Data, including without limitation,encryption technologies and authentication tools. Note,however that no data transmitted over the internet is 100% secure and any information disclosed online can potentially be collected and used by parties other than the intended recipient. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our Services.\n\nTRANSFERRING YOUR PERSONAL DATA OVERSEAS\n\nWe manage our Services through our teams around the world, including our teams in the United states, India and European Union We acknowledge that the data protection laws may be different from country to country, and may not provide the same level of protection If you visit our Services or contact us from outside of the United States, please be advised that(i) any information you provide to us or that we automatically collect may be transferred to the United States and other countries where our teams are located; and (ii) that by using our Services or submitting information, you explicitly authorize its transfer to and subsequent processing in the United States and other countries where our teams are located in accordance with this Privacy Statement. If you have any questions about our policies for transferring your Personal Data, please contact us as stated below.\n\nCHILDREN\'S PRIVACY\n\nWe respect the privacy of children Our services are not designed to attract an audience younger than 16, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under 16. Please contact us using the contact details below if you believe we may have collected information from your child, and we will work to delete\n\nTHIRD-PARTY LINKS AND SERVICES\n\nWe provide links to third party websites operated by organizations not affiliated with LinkupHome We do not disclose your Personal Data to organizations operating such linked third-party websites. We do not review or endorse, and are not responsible for the privacy practices of these organizations We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that you visit. This Privacy Statement applies solely to information collected by LinkupHome through the Services.\n\nCHANGES TO THE PRIVACY STATEMENT\n\nFrom time to time, we may modify this privacy Statement to accommodate new technology, industry practices, regulatory requirements, or for other purposes. If we make material changes to this privacy Statement that would impact your continued use of the Services, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you of such changes(including through email, push message, and/or by posting a notice directly to your account), and may also ask you to affirmatively consent to the changes at the time of your next login to the Services. By continuing to use the Services after such notice and/or consent, you agree to be bound by Privacy Statement as modified. If you do not agree with our changes to Privacy Statement, your sole and exclusive remedy will be to discontinue use of the Services.\n\nQUESTIONS AND FEEDBACK\n\nWe welcome your questions and comments about this Privacy Statement or our privacy practices. You can also contact us to exercise your privacy rights under applicable law. You can contact us as follows:\n\nNINGBO HOMEY PHOTOELECTRIC TECH. CO., LTD\nNo. 65 Mu Jin Road, High Technical Zone, Ningbo, China\nhttp://www.ihomey.cc/\n\n</string>
    <string name="license_agreement_content">IMPORTANT: Please read this End User License Agreement (“EULA”) carefully. It is very important that you ensure that you are purchasing rights to (or are provided with) link up home software Applications or product from an approved source and that you,or the entity you represent have been registered as the end user for the purpose of this EULA.If you are not registered as the end user you have no license to use the Application.Assuming you have purchased rights(or were supplied with access rights to the Application) from an approved source, the downloading, installing or use of the Application constitutes acceptance of this EULA. Please read this EULA carefully before installing the Application.\n\nThis EULA is binding between you, as the original purchaser(or original recipient) and Linkup home International industries,incorporated and its affiliates for the software,services and support material,if any,that are the subject matter of this EULA.Apple,Inc.(“Apple”)is not a party to this EULA and is not responsible for any content related to the Application.You agree that Apple and Apple’s subsidiaries are third party beneficiaries under this EULA,an upon acceptance of the terms and conditions of this EULA, Apple will have the right to enforce the EULA against you as a third party beneficiary of the EULA.\n\n1. BACKGROUND\n\n1.1.You desire to license the Application for the sole purpose of installing or using the Application in the operation and/or maintenance of a Linkuphome product.1.2 LinkupHome desires to license such Application to you for use exclusively in connection with a LinkupHome product.Such use shall be at your sole risk.You and Linkup home further agree as follows:\n\n2. DEFINITIONS\n\n2.1.“Affiliates” shall mean with respect to LinkupHome, a person or entity that,directly or indirectly,controls,is controlled by,or is under common control with LinkupHome. With respect to an Affiliate,control shall mean the possession,directly or the actions and/or policies and management of a person or entity,whether by the ownership of stock,by ownership of voting security,by contract or by other method.\n\n2.2.“You” or “your” shall mean the person or entity accepting this EULA,and uses the Application for the product.\n\n2.3.“Product” shall mean the LinkupHome-branded product intended for use with the Application.\n\n2.4 “Application” shall mean the software,software components and related documentation(hard copy and/or electronic copies) that accompany this EULA and that corresponds to the software program that was purchased from or was provided by an authorized LinkupHome source.\n\n3. LICENSE\n\n3.1.Download, installation and/or use of the Application constitutes acceptance of this EULA.This EULA and any related policies found in embedded links may be periodically updated.\n\n3.2.LinkupHome grants yo you a non-exclusive and non-transferable license to use the Application on one Apple device that you own or control,exclusively for the purpose of use with products,and as permitted by the usage rules set forth in Apple’s App Store Terms and Conditions.This license does not represent a sale of software or permission to lend, sell, redistribute, sub license, lease or rent the Application to other parties.\n\n3.3.LinkupHome retains all rights,title and interest in and to the Application.\n\n4. LICENSE RESTRICTIONS\n\n4.1.This license does not allow use of the Application on any device that you do not own or control.\n\n4.2.Use on a network or on multiple devices at the same time is strictly prohibited.\n\n4.3.The Application may not be copied or reproduced in whole or in part except for archival purposes of the Application components through authorized use or as permitted by law.\n\n4.4.You shall not remove any notices,including but not limited to copyright,trademark,or other proprietary rights notices,or any disclaimers or warning notices included on or embedded in the Application.\n\n4.5.You may not transfer,transmit,or export the Application in whole or in part to another user useless expressly authorized under this EULA.\n\n4.6.You shall not make any attempt to disassemble,decompile,reverse engineer or otherwise convert any part of the Application to a human-perceivable form or assist or attempt to assist another person to do the same.\n\n4.7.You shall not modify the Application in any manner.\n\n4.8.Your rights in the Application shall be limited to those expressly granted in this EULA.\n\n4.9.The Application may enable access to LinkupHome’s and other third party services and web sites (collectively and individually, “services”). Use of the services may require internet access for which you must accept other additional terms of service,for which neither LinkupHome nor Apple are liable to you for any losses,damages, or claims.\n\n5. SERVICES\n\n5.1 You understand that by using any of the services.You may encounter content that may be deemed offensive,indecent,or objectionable,which content may or may not be identified as having explicit language,and that the results of any search or entering of a particular URL may automatically and unintentionally generate links or references to objectionable material.Nevertheless,you agree to us the services at your sole risk and acknowledge that Apple has no obligation to furnish any services relate to the Application.Neither LinkupHome nor Apple shall have any liability to you for content that may be found to be offensive,indecent,or objectionable.\n\n5.2 Certation Services may display,include or make available content, data, information, applications or materials from third parties (“Third Party Materials”) or provide links to certain third party web sites.By using the the Services, you acknowledge and agree that LinkupHome and Apple are not responsible for examining or evaluating the  content, accuracy, completeness, timeliness, validity, copyright compliance, legality, decency, quality or any other aspect of such third party materials or websites. Neither LinkupHome nor Apple warrant, endorse, or assume any liability or responsibility to you or any other person for any other person for any third-party services, third party materials or web sites, or for any other materials,products,or services of third parties. Third party materials and links to other web sites are provided solely as a convenience to you.Financial information displayed by any services is for general informational purposes only and is not intended to be relied upon as investment advice.Before executing any securities transaction based upon information obtained through the services,you should consult with a financial professional. Location data provided by any services is for basic navigational purposes only and is not intended to be relied upon in situations where precise location information is needed or where erroneous,inaccurate or incomplete location data may lead to death,personal injury,property or environmental damage.Neither Apple, LinkupHome nor any of its content providers, guarantees the availability, accuracy, completeness, reliability, or timeliness of stock information or location data displayed by any services.\n\n5.3 You agree that services may contain proprietary content,information and material that is protected by applicable intellectual property and other laws,including but not limited to copyright, and that you will not use such proprietary content, information and material that is protected by applicable intellectual property and other laws,including but not limited to copyright, and that you will not use such proprietary content,information or materials in any way, expect for permitted use of the services. No portion of the services may be reproduced in any form or by any means. You agree nor to modify, rent, lease, loan, sell, distribute, or create derivative works based on the services, in any manner,and you shall not exploit the services in any unauthorized way whatsoever,including but not limited to,by trespass burdening network capacity. You further agree not to use the service in any manner to harass, abuse, stalk, threaten,  defame or otherwise infringe or violate the rights of any other party,and that neither LinkupHome or Apple is not in any way responsible for any such use by you,nor for any harassing, threatening, defamatory, offensive or illegal messages or transmissions that you may receive as a result of using any of services.\n\n5.4 In addition,third party services and Third Party Materials that may be accessed from,displayed on, or linked to or from authorized devices or platforms are not available in all languages or in all countries. Neither LinkupHome or Apple make any representation that such services and Materials and appropriate or available for use in any particular location. To the extent you choose to access such services or materials, you do so at your own initiative and are responsible for compliance with any applicable laws, including but not limited to applicable laws,LinkupHome and its licensors, reserve the right to change, suspend,remove, or disable access to any services in its control at any time without notice.In no event will LinkupHome be liable for the removal of or disabling of access to any such services.LinkupHome may also impose limits on the use of or access to certain services within its control, in any case and without notice or liability.\n\n6. PROPRIETARY RIGHTS\n\n6.1 All intellectual property rights in the Application and all modifications,updates,upgrades to and derivative works based upon the Application belong solely to LinkupHome,and you do not acquire any rights in them.\n\n6.2 LinkupHome reserves the sole and exclusive right at its discretion to assert claims against third parties for infringement or misappropriation of its intellectual property rights in the Application.\n\n6.3 In the event of any third party claim that the Application or your possession and use of the Application or your possession and use of the Application infringes the rights of a third party,you acknowledge that LinkupHome and not Apple will be solely responsible for the investigation, defense, settlement, and discharge of any such intellectual property claim.\n\n7. CONSENT TO USE DATA\n\n7.1 You agrees that LinkupHome may collect and use technical data and related information, including but not limited to technical information about the device,system,Application software,and peripherals,that is gathered periodically to facilitate the provision of software updates,product support,and other services related to the Application.LinkupHome may use this data,as long as it does not personally identify you,to improve its products or to provide services or technologies to you.\n\n7.2 The Application collects and processes data with Google Analytics. How Google uses data is described in the link below for Google Analytics. The LinkupHome privacy policy at the link below describes how you may consent to the storing and accessing of cookies and other information on your Application.\n\n8. TERMINATION\n\n8.1 Without prejudice to any other rights, LinkupHome may terminate this EULA without notice if you fails to comply with the terms and condition of this EULA.\n\n8.2 You may terminate this EULA without notice to LinkupHome by ceasing use of and destroying all copies of the Application,including all archival copies.\n\n8.3 Upon termination of the EULA for any reason,you shall immediately cease use of the Application,and destroy all copies of the Application,including all archival copies.\n\n9. YOUR REPRESENTATIONS\n\n9.1 If you are a company, the acceptor of this EULA warrants that he/she has the authority to contract on behalf of and bind your company.If you are an individual,you represent that you have the legal capacity to enter into a binding agreement and you are of the age of consent.\n\n10. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES\n\n10.1 To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law,LinkupHome provides the Application and services “as is” and with all faults.Linkuohome disclaims all other warranties,whether express,implied or statutory,or arising by custom or trade usage,including but not limited to the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose,and non-infringement of third party rights.\n\n10.2 LinkupHome provides the Application without warranty of accuracy, satisfactory quality, title, quiet enjoyment, or quite possession. LinkupHome does not warrant that the operation of the Application or services will be uninterrupted or services will be uninterrupted or error-free, or that defects in the Application or services will be corrected, no oral or written information or advice given by LinkupHome or its authorized representative shall create a warranty. Should the Application or services prove defective,you assume the entire cost of all necessary serving repair, or correction.\n\n10.3 You and LinkupHome acknowledge that Apple does not have any warranty obligation for the Application, and to the extent permitted under the law, any claims, losses, liabilities, damages, costs, or expenses attributable to any failure to conform to any warranty will by your responsibility.\n\n10.4 In the event of any failure of the Application to conform to its warranty, you may notify apple, and Apple will refund the purchase price of the Application to You. Any other claims, losses, liabilities, damages costs, or expenses attributable to any failure to conform to any warranty shall be your sole responsibility.\n\n11. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY\n\n11.1 If You acquired the Application in the United States, Latin America, the Caribbean or Canada, regardless of whether any remedy set forth in this EULA fails its essential purpose, in no event will LinkupHome or its suppliers be liable for any lost revenue, profit, or lost or damaged data, business interruption, loss of capital, or special, indirect, consequential incidental or punitive damages however caused regardless of the theory of liability, or whether arising out of the use of or inability to use the Application, and even if LinkupHome or its suppliers or licensors have been advised of the possibility of such damages. Because some States or jurisdictions do not allow limitation or exclusion of consequential or incidental damages, the above limitation may not apply to You.\n\n11.2 If You acquired the software in Japan, except for liability arising out of or in connection with death or personal injury, fraudulent misrepresentation, and regardless of whether any remedy fails its essential purpose, in no event will LinkupHome, its affiliates, officers,directors, employees, agents, suppliers and licensors be liable for any lost revenue, profit, or lost or damaged data, business interruption loss of capital, or for special, indirect, consequential, incidental, or punitivedamages however caused and regardless of the theory of liability, or whether arising out of the use of or inability to use the Application, even if LinkupHome or any approved source or their suppliers or licensors have been advised of the possibility of such damages.\n\n11.3 If You acquired the software in Europe, the Middle East, Africa, Asia or Oceania, in no event will LinkupHome its affiliates, officers directors employees agents suppliers and licensors, be liable for any lost revenue,lost profit, or lost or damaged data, business interruption, loss of capital, or for special, indirect consequential, incidental, or punitive damages, whether arising in contract or tort(including negligence), or whether arising out of the use of or inability to use the Application, even if, in each case, LinkupHome, its affiliates,officers directors employees agents suppliers and licensors, have been advised of the possibility of such damages. because some states or jurisdictions do not allow the limitation or exclusion of consequential or incidental damages, the above limitation may not fully apply to You. The foregoing exclusion shall not apply to any liability arising out of or in connection with: (i)death or personal injury, (ii) fraudulent misrepresentation, or (ii) LinkupHome\'s liability in connection with any terms that cannot be excluded under applicable law.\n\n11.4 LinkupHome, and not Apple, is solely responsible to You and any third parties to address any third party claims arising from the use or possession of the Application,including but not limited to: ()infringement, (i) product liability claims, (ii) any claim that the Application fails to conform to any applicable legal or regulatory requirement, and (iv) any claims arising under consumer protection or similar legislation.\n\n11.5 In no event shall LinkupHome total liability to You of all damages (other than as may be required by applicable law in cases involving personal injury) exceed $50. The foregoing limitations shall apply to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, even if any remedy fails its essential purpose.\n\n12. DISCLAIMERS\n\n12.1 If You acquired the Application in the United States of America, Latin America, Canada, Japan or the Caribbean, notwithstanding any damages that You might incur for any reason, the download, installation and use of the Application is at Your sole risk. LinkupHome disclaims all liability with respect to damages arising from or caused directly or indirectly by the Application the installation process for the Application or arising from or caused by this EULA.\n\n12.2 If You acquired the Application in Europe, the Middle East, Africa, Asia or Oceania, notwithstanding any damages that You might incur for any reason, the download, installation and use of the Application is at Your sole risk. LinkupHome disclaims all liability with respect to damages arising from or caused directly or indirectly, by the Application, the installation process for the Application or arising from or caused by this EULA Nothing in the EULA shall limit(i)the liability of LinkupHome,its affiliates, officers, directors, employees, agents,suppliers and licensors to You for personal injury or death caused by their negligence, (i) LinkupHome\'s liability for fraudulent misrepresentation, or(ii)any liability of LinkupHome which cannot be excluded under applicable law.\n\n12.3 The foregoing disclaimers shall apply to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, even if any remedy fails its essential purpose.\n\nEULA END\n\n</string>



    <string name="lamp_c3">Outdoor Light</string>
    <string name="lamp_r2">RGB Bulb</string>
    <string name="lamp_a2">CCT Bulb</string>
    <string name="lamp_n1">RGB Strip Light</string>
    <string name="lamp_m1">Bedside Lamp</string>
    <string name="lamp_v1">Mini Garden light</string>
    <string name="lamp_s1">RGB Spotlight</string>
    <string name="lamp_s2">CCT Spotlight</string>
    <string name="lamp_t1">RGB Downlight</string>
    <string name="lamp_t1_rgb">RGB</string>
    <string name="lamp_t1_cct">CCT</string>


    <string name="zones_title">Home</string>
    <string name="zone_create_title">Create new home</string>
    <string name="zone_create_hint">A new home for your LinkupHome devices.\nPlease name it.</string>
    <string name="zone_name_default">Home</string>
    <string name="zones_empty_hint">Create a room, easy manage devices</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips</string>

    <string name="rename_tip">Tap to rename</string>
    <string name="bind_device_tip">Tap here , add available devices to the room</string>
    <string name="devices_title">Device</string>
    <string name="devices_empty_hint">No devices, please add</string>
    <string name="action_add_device">Add device</string>
    <string name="choose_device_type_title">Device type</string>
    <string name="search_device_title">Search devices</string>
    <string name="device_connect_step1_title">Are you ready?</string>
    <string name="device_connect_step1_hint">1.Make sure the device is correctly powered.\n2.If it was not the initial installation, please reset your device.</string>
    <string name="next_step">Next Step</string>
    <string name="searching">Searching</string>
    <string name="how_to_reset_device">How to reset</string>
    <string name="how_to_reset_device_step1">Step 1</string>
    <string name="how_to_reset_device_step2">Step 2</string>
    <string name="how_to_reset_step">Reset Steps</string>
    <string name="how_to_reset_process">Reset Steps</string>
    <string name="bridge_disconnected">The device is disconnected , trying to connect automatically</string>
    <string name="connect_device_title">Connecting devices</string>
    <string name="state_disconnected">Tap to connect</string>
    <string name="state_connected">Connected</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="delete_device_hint">Do you want to disconnect and delete device?</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="confirm">Yes</string>
    <string name="join">Join</string>

    <string name="choose_room_type_title">Room type</string>
    <string name="create_room_title">Name a new room</string>
    <string name="delete_room_title">Delete room</string>
    <string name="delete_room_hint">Do you want to delete current room?</string>
    <string name="light_cycling_spped">Light change speed</string>
    <string name="available_devices_title"> Available devices</string>
    <string name="bind_device_change_title">Modified not saved</string>
    <string name="bind_device_change_hint">The modified data has not been saved, are you sure to exit?</string>


    <string name="setting_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="setting_current_home">Current home</string>
    <string name="setting_language">Language</string>
    <string name="setting_user_manual">User manual</string>
    <string name="setting_faqs">FAQs</string>
    <string name="setting_more">More</string>
    <string name="setting_action_delete_devices">Go to device list</string>

    <string name="zone_delete_hint1">Please reserve at least one home for adding devices</string>
    <string name="zone_delete_hint2">Devices in the current home are still connected, please go to the device list to delete devices one by one, then you can delete the current home.</string>
    <string name="zone_share_title">Share a home</string>
    <string name="zone_share_invitation_code">My Invitation Code</string>
    <string name="zone_join_title">Join a home</string>
    <string name="zone_share_tip1">1.The sharing function only can be available when connect to the network. Please make sure the WiFi or network is turned on in mobile phone.</string>
    <string name="zone_share_tip2">2.Share the automatically generated invitation code with your family and friends.</string>
    <string name="zone_share_tip3">3.The invitee also needs to connect to the network,  enter into "join a home" and input the invitation code to control the lights together.</string>
    <string name="zone_share_notes">Notes:  </string>
    <string name="zone_share_warning">if several persons want to control lights toghter, please make sure the lights (need to be turned on) no less than mobile devices (mobile phones/IPADs). Otherwise, some mobile devices cannot connect and control the lights.It means how many lights on, how many persons can control toghter.</string>
    <string name="zone_join_tip1">Request home host to create invitation code and share it with you.  (settings → share a home→  select a home → generate invitation code→  share invitation code)</string>
    <string name="zone_join_tip2">Input the invitation code below:</string>
    <string name="language_setting_title">Language Settings</string>


</resources>
